<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<blog>
	<item>
		<title>Hello ESN!</title>
		<summary><![CDATA[<p>This is the new ESN Satellite Blog.</p><!]]></summary>
		<body><![CDATA[<p>The IT Committee introduces a new feature to Satellite 4.4: the <strong>Satellite Blog</strong></p>
		<p>With the new blog feature you can add blog posts including an image, categories and comment support.
			Categories can be configured at <a href="admin/structure/taxonomy/blog_category" target="_blank">admin/structure/taxonomy/blog_category</a>,
			Comments can be configured at <a href="admin/structure/types/manage/blog" target="_blank">admin/structure/types/manage/blog</a>
			and managed at <a href="admin/content/comment" target="_blank">admin/content/comment</a>.
		</p><!]]></body>
		<image>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/itcom.png</image>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>ESN Gift Exchange</title>
		<summary><![CDATA[<p>The weather starts to get colder, nights are getting darker, snow starts to cover the landscape, these
			are the signs to know something special in ESN is getting closer, a time to share something special with your
			fellow ESNers, how?<br /><u><strong>Obviusly with the ESN Gift Exchange!</strong></u></p><!]]></summary>
		<body><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:justify">The weather starts to get colder, nights are getting darker, snow starts to
			cover the landscape, these are the signs to know something special in ESN is getting closer, a time to share
			something special with your fellow ESNers, how?<br><u><strong>Obviusly with the ESN Gift Exchange!</strong></u>
			</p>
			<p style="text-align:justify">Yes, Gift Exchnage is already here, conNECting the ESN Network, from South to North,
				from East to West, so it's members can exchange smiles, knowledge and whatever you feel like giving to make the
				day to a fellow ESNer. How you can take part in this wonderful experience? Very simple, first of all you need to
				be ESNer, convince your local Board, your National Board or your NR to sign up to the Gift Exchange and after
				that you will receive more instructions, if you want to know more, have a peak in the FAQ page of the level you
				want to take part in (Local or National).</p>
			<p style="text-align:justify">Don't wait, sign up now! The registration will be open until the <strong>30th of
				November!</strong> So don't start your hibernation yet.</p>
			<p style="text-align:justify">If you have any questions, don't hesitate to contact the dedicated office for ESN in
				the Santa Village (The Gift Exchange Team) <a href="mailto:giftexchange@esn.org">giftexchange@esn.org</a>.</p>
		<!]]></body>
		<image>profiles/satellite/modules/content/files/esn_gift_exchange.png</image>
	</item>
</blog>